const quizzes = [
  {
    title: "How to Invest",
    link: "how-to-invest",
    questions: [
      {
        question:
          "What is EDITDA most commonly used for in evaluating a company?",
        answers: [
          "Evaluate which of its products are most successful",
          "To gauge the company’s overall finanical health and performance. ",
          "Analyzing a company’s cash flow",
          "Analyze the quality of a company’s earnings",
        ],
        correct: 1,
      },
      {
        question: "How To Invest Q2",
        answers: ["option 1", "option 2 ", "option 3"],
        correct: 1,
      },
      {
        question: "How To Invest Q3",
        answers: ["option 1", "option 2 ", "option 3", "option 4"],
        correct: 3,
      },
      {
        question: "How To Invest Q4",
        answers: ["option 1", "option 2 ", "option 3", "option 4", "option 5"],
        correct: 2,
      },
    ],
  },

  {
    title: "Company",
    link: "company",
    questions: [
      {
        question: "companyin evaluating a company?",
        answers: [
          "Evaluate which of its products are most successful",
          "To gauge the company’s overall finanical health and performance. ",
          "Analyzing a company’s cash flow",
          "Analyze the quality of a company’s earnings",
        ],
        correct: 1,
      },
      {
        question: "What a company?",
        answers: [
          "Evaluate which of its products are  successful",
          "To  the  overall finanical health and performance. ",
          " a company’s cash flow",
          " the quality of a  earnings",
        ],
        correct: 1,
      },
      {
        question: "What ise valuating a company?",
        answers: [
          "Evaluate which of most successful",
          "To gauge terall finanical health and performance. ",
          "Analyzing cash flow",
          "Analyze earnings",
        ],
        correct: 1,
      },
    ],
  },

  {
    title: "Investing",
    link: "investing",
    questions: [
      {
        question: "What is EDITDA most commonly used  in evaluating a company?",
        answers: [
          "Evaluate  of its  are most successful",
          "To gaugs overall finanical health and performance. ",
          "Analyzing a company’s  flow",
          "Analyze tmpany’s earnings",
        ],
        correct: 1,
      },
      {
        question: "What is EDITDAa company?",
        answers: [
          "Evaluate which  its products are most successful",
          "To gauge t’s overall finanical health and performance. ",
          "Analyzing a  cash flow",
          "Analyze the  of a company’s earnings",
        ],
        correct: 1,
      },
      {
        question: "What is 28368243",
        answers: [
          "Evaluate w products are most successful",
          "To gauge ny’s overall finanical health and performance. ",
          "Analyzing a ’s cash flow",
          "Analyze the quany’s earnings",
        ],
        correct: 1,
      },
    ],
  },
];

// const quizzes = [
//   {
//     title: "How to Invest",
//     questions: [
//       {
//         question:
//           "What is EDITDA most commonly used for in evaluating a company?",
//         answers: ["", "", "", ""],
//         correct: 3,
//       },
//       {
//         question: "",
//         answers: ["", "", "", ""],
//         correct: 3,
//       },
//       {
//         question: "",
//         answers: ["", "", "", ""],
//         correct: 3,
//       },
//     ],
//   },

//   {
//     title: "Company",
//     questions: [
//       {
//         question:
//           "What is EDITDA most commonly used for in evaluating a company?",
//         answers: [
//           "Evaluate which of its products are most successful",
//           "To gauge the company’s overall finanical health and performance. ",
//           "Analyzing a company’s cash flow",
//           "Analyze the quality of a company’s earnings",
//         ],
//         correct: 1,
//       },
//       {
//         question: "",
//         answers: ["", "", "", ""],
//         correct: 3,
//       },
//       {
//         question: "",
//         answers: ["", "", "", ""],
//         correct: 3,
//       },
//     ],
//   },

//   {
//     title: "Investing",
//     questions: [
//       {
//         question:
//           "What is EDITDA most commonly used for in evaluating a company?",
//         answers: ["", "", "", ""],
//         correct: 3,
//       },
//       {
//         question: "",
//         answers: ["", "", "", ""],
//         correct: 3,
//       },
//       {
//         question: "",
//         answers: ["", "", "", ""],
//         correct: 3,
//       },
//     ],
//   },
// ];

export default quizzes;
